topic = "Irregular verbs. Write 2nd and 3rd forms of a verb.";
cards = [
 {"question":"be",
  "answer": ["was been", "were been"],
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bear",
  "answer": "bore borne",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"beat",
  "answer": "beat beaten",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"become",
  "answer": "became become",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"begin",
  "answer": "began begun",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bend",
  "answer": "bent bent",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bet",
  "answer": "bet bet",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bind",
  "answer": "bound bound",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bite",
  "answer": "bit bitten",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bleed",
  "answer": "bled bled",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"blow",
  "answer": "blew blown",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"break",
  "answer": "broke broken",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"bring",
  "answer": "brought brought",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"build",
  "answer": "built built",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"burn",
  "answer": ["burnt burnt","burned burned"],
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": [],
  "comment": "burnt burnt UK, burned burned US",
  "minor": "yes"},
 {"question":"burst",
  "answer": "burst burst",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"buy",
  "answer": "bought bought",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"cast",
  "answer": "cast cast",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
  {"question":"catch",
    "answer": "caught caught",
    "radios": [],
    "arg1": []},
  {"question":"choose",
  "answer": "chose chosen",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"come",
  "answer": "came come",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"cost",
  "answer": "cost cost",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"cut",
  "answer": "cut cut",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"deal",
  "answer": "dealt dealt",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"dig",
  "answer": "dug dug",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"do",
  "answer": "did done",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"draw",
  "answer": "drew drawn",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"dream",
  "answer": ["dreamt dreamt","dream dream"],
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"drink",
  "answer": "drank drunk",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"drive",
  "answer": "drove driven",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"eat",
  "answer": "ate eaten",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"fall",
  "answer": "fell fallen",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
  {"question":"feed",
    "answer": "fed fed",
    "radios": [],
    "arg1": []},
 {"question":"feel",
  "answer": "felt felt",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"fight",
  "answer": "fought fought",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"find",
  "answer": "found found",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"fly",
  "answer": "flew flown",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"forbid",
  "answer": "forbade forbidden",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"forget",
  "answer": "forgot forgotten",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"forgive",
  "answer": "forgave forgiven",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"get",
  "answer": "got got",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"give",
  "answer": "gave given",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"go",
  "answer": "went gone",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"grow",
  "answer": "grew grown",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"hang",
  "answer": "hung hung",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"have",
  "answer": "had had",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"hear",
  "answer": "heard heard",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"hide",
  "answer": "hid hidden",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"hit",
  "answer": "hit hit",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"hold",
  "answer": "held held",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"hurt",
  "answer": "hurt hurt",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"keep",
  "answer": "kept kept",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"know",
  "answer": "knew known",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"lay (put something on something)",
  "answer": "laid laid",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"lead",
  "answer": "led led",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"learn",
  "answer": ["learnt learnt","learned learned"],
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": [],
  "comment": "learnt learnt UK, learned learned US",
  "minor": "yes"},
 {"question":"leave",
  "answer": "left left",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"lend",
  "answer": "lent lent",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"let",
  "answer": "let let",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
{"question":"lie (on a bed)",
  "answer": "lay lain",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"lose",
  "answer": "lost lost",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"make",
  "answer": "made made",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"mean",
  "answer": "meant meant",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"meet",
  "answer": "met met",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"mislead",
  "answer": "misled misled",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"overcome",
  "answer": "overcame overcome",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"overhear",
  "answer": "overheard overheard",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"oversleep",
  "answer": "overslept overslept",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"pay",
  "answer": "paid paid",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"put",
  "answer": "put put",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"read",
  "answer": "read read",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"rid",
  "answer": "rid rid",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"ride",
  "answer": "rode ridden",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"ring",
  "answer": "rang rung",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"rise",
  "answer": "rose risen",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"run",
  "answer": "ran run",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"say",
  "answer": "said said",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"see",
  "answer": "saw seen",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"seek",
  "answer": "sought sought",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sell",
  "answer": "sold sold",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"send",
  "answer": "sent sent",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"set",
  "answer": "set set",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"shake",
  "answer": "shook shaken",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"shine",
  "answer": "shone shone",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"shoot",
  "answer": "shot shot",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"show",
  "answer": "showed shown",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"shut",
  "answer": "shut shut",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sing",
  "answer": "sang sung",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sink",
  "answer": "sank sunk",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sit",
  "answer": "sat sat",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sleep",
  "answer": "slept slept",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"slide",
  "answer": "slid slid",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"smell",
  "answer": "smelt smelt",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"speak",
  "answer": "spoke spoken",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"spell",
  "answer": "spelt spelt",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"spend",
  "answer": "spent spent",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"spin",
  "answer": "spun spun",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"split",
  "answer": "split split",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"spread",
  "answer": "spread spread",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"stand",
  "answer": "stood stood",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"steal",
  "answer": "stole stolen",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"stick",
  "answer": "stuck stuck",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sting",
  "answer": "stung stung",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"strike",
  "answer": "struck struck",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"swear",
  "answer": "swore sworn",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"sweep",
  "answer": "swept swept",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"swim",
  "answer": "swam swum",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"swing",
  "answer": "swung swung",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"take",
  "answer": "took taken",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"teach",
  "answer": "taught taught",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"tell",
  "answer": "told told",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"think",
  "answer": "thought thought",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"throw",
  "answer": "threw thrown",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"wake",
  "answer": "woke woken",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"wear",
  "answer": "wore worn",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"win",
  "answer": "won won",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
 {"question":"write",
  "answer": "wrote written",
  "radios": [],
  "arg1": []},
]


include("js/engine.js",function(){
  //
});
